FANSUB GROUP AZALIA PRESENTS
Worked on the series:
Lily, Tiramisu, Biryulka, Host, February, Zinger
How did I become
queen
Why did you expose yourself to attack?
AZALEA
There he is!
Let's forget about distancing today.
Your Majesty.
Are you okay?
Who's there?
We're leaving, heading out.
Episode 9
I let them sleep separately
to rest in peace,
but it seems I was a little mistaken.
I heard something break.
I also woke up because of the noise.
And the door was broken.
The matter is clearly unclean, everything needs to be examined.
But then we will interrupt the royal couple.
I wouldn't be surprised if because of them
the house will shake.
Newlyweds, what to take from them.
We must protect their privacy.
Don't get too close to the house.
Yes.
I'll go to the annex.
Will you protect their peace?
-Yes.
-Take care of them.
Control yourself, woman!
And you had to kiss him?!
Are you looking for a fight?
Who are you arguing with?
Don't interfere.
This is just between me and Kim Soyeon.
While I'm here
I will do what I want with this body.
Whose soul is in the body is the owner!
Apparently you're still drunk.
You don't see the difference between a dream and reality.
-I have a stone in my soul.
-What are you talking about?
Yes, I'm in any condition
I can walk home on my own two feet.
No. This is not a dream.
Why would you show up in my dream?
Sorry for showing up
in your dreams.
Forget this nightmare.
Episode 9: Light and Darkness
Hong Young, it's ticklish.
She's not here. If she is not in the house, then where?
Is something wrong?
It wasn't because of the past that he was worried.
-Hey, hey.
-What?
They told me not to come near the house.
-Why?
-Don't know.
-Sit down.
-Fine.
To be honest, I'm worried about Her Majesty.
Have you heard anything about her?
About the queen?
She runs around the palace
every morning.
Don't talk nonsense.
I have known her since infancy.
She never ran when she was born.
-You're lying.
-It's true.
-And it’s strange.
-But that's what they say.
-No.
-I don’t believe it!
I'm telling the truth.
-Chickens!
-Grab them.
Stop, feathered one!
He wore the clothes of the Detective Department.
So...
You'll get so drunk. Stop.
Thirst torments.
The more I think what a sin it is,
the more I thirst.
It's like I'm dying of thirst.
If you're thirsty, drink water, not wine.
Hey there, bring us some water.
Yes.
The more wine you drink, the more you want to drink.
I slept so well, as if someone had knocked me out.
I understand you.
The body was filled with lightness.
You. You.
This house must have been built on good soil. I had a great night's sleep.
Is it normal that you wake up with me?
Is this abnormal?
This is not a palace - you don’t choose the date of your night together.
Naturally, in our father’s house we share the same bed.
Logical.
You have to be in the camp of the enemy
with me is the best cover.
Your game today is top class.
Okay, let's pretend
that we spent a hot night together.
It was so hot that we turned it over...
What?
It seems you remember this night.
It would be a pity if you forgot her
like our first one.
Is it because the memory has returned?
I sleep like a baby.
I have no time to play tricks.
You need to become the queen dowager's ace.
Even if something happens to the Han family,
They can't reach me.
The masked man and I were looking for the same thing.
How much does Kim Byungin already know?
The accounting book should not fall into their hands.
Today I will return to the palace no matter what.
Today I will find the book no matter what.
You can get sick that way.
When does the queen return to the palace?
I will send word so that they are with His Majesty
returned as soon as possible.
I never found life in the palace boring.
But the queen has only been gone for a couple of days,
and here it’s already desolate.
Is Her Majesty's cooking so exquisite?
It's not about her cooking.
She's nice to me.
Attachment is dangerous.
This morning I was hungry...
That is
I woke up early, missing my dear queen.
I understand you.
It's scary to realize that you've been tamed.
It seems like you're the one using others
but at some point it turns out that you have been tamed.
Therefore, you must find more people who are useful to you.
I will order the royal chefs
learn Her Majesty's recipes.
You made my life in the palace a paradise.
I have no reason to leave him.
That's why I ended up in my place -
to guard this paradise, Your Majesty.
By the way.
Tell Benin to come see me sometimes.
Do you want
talk to him?
After all, he is your adopted son.
I've neglected him enough.
It's time to give him instructions from time to time.
You're still not getting any younger.
Do only important things.
Everything that concerns you is important to me.
What are you doing?
Detective department
will check each of the king's guards.
You protect the life of the king and are always by his side -
we must make sure of everything.
Don't let them take a step!
Every person here has passed
full check.
You can also buy a pedigree.
You never know.
Someone from the guard
may be preparing treason under someone else's name.
Provide assistance - we are doing our duty.
If you do not find evidence of your accusations,
I
I will now use my powers.
That is if you save your post.
If you are not involved in treason, move away.
-Look everywhere.
-Yes.
Search every corner.
Seize all documents.
And bring it to the Detective Department.
-Yes!
Hope you slept well.
I brought a beautiful bird.
How do you like her?
She has beautiful plumage.
This precious bird makes me happy in the light of the good news.
Got some good news?
Enmity between the queen and
Royal Concubine Cho is even stronger than I thought.
There's something I didn't tell you.
Nobody knows about this.
Just me and the queen.
Because of what happened 8 years ago, Her Majesty is confident
that I stole the king from her.
The poison on our arrow is getting stronger.
It's time to use the second thing.
Yes.
It's hard to find something as similar
this will take me some time.
But I'll bring it to you
even if you have to make it yourself.
Use this one.
They will know about the royal guard in no time.
Let's find a way.
Yesterday you ran into a man from the Detective Department.
He saw your face. Will this be a problem?
I don't think he recognized me.
If we collide again
he will understand that I was looking for the ledger.
He was wearing a rare mask in the form of a tokkebi.
Did he have a scar?
Yes. It looks like an old scar.
He is one of those who tortured Ovol.
So Kim Jwageun
acted through Kim Byonin.
Fortunately,
he does not know that the location of the ledger has changed.
Tonight is our last chance.
Your Majesty, there is a letter for you from the palace.
This letter is from Kim Jwageun.
He was delivered by the head of the Detective Department.
Anyone from this department
could easily deliver it.
But did you personally complain?
Do you have a lot of free time?
I brought it personally because it's important.
Your Majesty and the Queen are asked to return to the palace immediately.
Troop commander
demands that I return to the palace?
He delivers a message from the Queen Dowager.
I will stay here another night for the queen's health.
-Tell them.
-But...
That's all.
Don't disturb the queen's peace and come back.
Here's how.
It seems His Majesty is very concerned about the Queen's health.
That's what I'll tell you.
I will have breakfast in the queen's room.
Bring your usual breakfast. Just let it be easy.
Yes, Your Majesty.
We will serve our usual breakfast.
Concubine Cho's house is nearby,
I'll find out about Ovol and come back.
Great idea.
I felt bad after sending her away.
And I won’t be in the palace for another night.
Please keep an eye on her.
Yes.
The Queen hung around here all day long. But when she was gone,
the royal kitchen seems so empty.
Now I can breathe again.
You scoundrel. More rapeseed oil.
Here's the armless one.
Cut it smaller.
Cook quickly before it loses its shape.
How nice and peaceful it is here.
I love being in charge.
-Royal cook!
- Yes, that's enough.
-Royal cook.
-Come back.
- We obey.
Court lady Choi.
Looking at your face
I realized that the queen had not yet recovered.
No, she made a full recovery.
Then why were they lowered into the water?
I've been through so much lately thanks to Her Majesty.
I thought when she wasn't around,
I won't have to find fault
and I will feel calmer.
But in reality, how?
I'm going even more crazy.
I'm scared to death that without me she'll get completely out of hand.
Here's the deal. They say that there are much more worries about unheard rumors,
than about kind kids.
Stop moping.
Here.
Open.
Picked it up along the way.
On days like these
you're like mine, but no.
And days like these you are like mine, but not.
And why did he give me the garbage he picked up?
What a nightmare.
The more I get to know him, the stranger it seems.
He could have just thrown it away, why did he give it to me?
This is rubbish.
Have you received news from Ovol?
No.
Did something happen to her?
She didn't return home.
I think she went somewhere else because she felt guilty towards you.
I asked around about her. Don't worry too much.
I told her so many times, but she again...
I'm looking for your gift for her.
If she went to another place, she had to sell it.
I'm scared
that I will lose all my people.
When will the king return to the palace?
He will stay
for one more night.
It's not what you think.
I can't tell you the details
but tonight everything will be resolved.
It's not that the king has
many other worries
his feelings for me have changed.
Apparently, I'm the only one clinging to childhood memories.
I remember how I returned to the capital
and met you and the king two years ago.
Even if that day was the first time he saw you,
for sure
I would love it.
Your words encourage me.
What is your usual breakfast?
I need to get better.
Why do you need to hang around here another night?
To take care of you, my queen.
Doctors treat, pharmacists give medicine.
And the king cares about politics,
and not about my health.
Do you know how much people suffer?
You speak the true truth, queen.
So come on, make some turtle soup
and go to work as a king.
Don't neglect the turtle's sacrifice.
Rather than accept her sacrifice, I'd rather go
I'll see how ordinary people live.
I'll be back late
which means you have to stay another night.
Don’t you want to hang around in the palace either?
It’s terrible that you feel even worse there than at your relatives’ house.
Yes, it's nice and cozy here.
What kind of person is the Queen Dowager?
She is Mr. Kim Jwageun's sister
and has not left the palace since she arrived.
What if I present to someone who never
did not leave the palace, dishes from outside...
You know...
In historical dramas, they always eat gukbap.
What does it taste like?
How can I know the taste of such simple food?
Not that amazing.
What you miss
can become a terrible weapon.
They made a broth from beef brisket and white radish,
seasoned with soybean paste and heated the rice with it.
It has a lot of meat. Modest, but it has its own charm.
Kimchi made from radish
no salted seafood,
because everything goes well together without overwhelming the taste.
It is said that Hongjong always ate gukbap outside the palace.
Damn it.
The neighbor ran away without paying taxes,
I have to pay for it.
This is a real robbery.
Bite your tongue.
Do you want to be beaten with sticks?
I'll die biting my tongue
or I’ll run away and become a bandit - there are two options.
Bite your tongue? Yes, I have nothing to lose!
They peel off like sticky stuff. Where is the king looking?!
What did you want?
Of course, he rips off.
A puppet who was given a throne to close
for all to see, and they did what they wanted.
Crap.
Stop.
I overheard you.
You've been through a lot.
People die because of a stupid king.
Drink and forget your sorrows.
You look alike
for a person of high position.
Pretending to be an aristocrat.
The most expensive thing was the pedigree.
Without clothes and pedigree, I am an ordinary beggar.
Young people today look great
but in reality they are dummies like you.
How dare you?
Yes, our country is a dummy.
If people had something inside them,
They would have taken that away too.
Funny.
This gentleman
- an interesting way of looking at things.
-Funny.
A man from a family of traitors became king.
Everything is completely rotten.
Where has it been seen that a person from a family
who for generations committed treason,
became a king?
What was the king thinking when accepting the throne?
He lives in the power of the Kims,
who cowardly killed his entire family.
That's it.
-Crap.
-And that’s true.
You have crossed the line.
You are free to curse the king,
but don't you dare discuss his family!
There is a line that cannot be crossed!
Do you think
Does being a king mean living a luxurious life?
He is constantly afraid of being poisoned
or headless. This is cruel!
Are you from the palace?
Are you representatives of the king?
Who are you?
I? Yes I am
from the King's fan club.
-What?
-What is this?
Fan club?
Antifans are fans too.
Okay, at least one more time discuss his family,
I'll turn the table over for you!
-Did you miss it?
-Okay, okay.
Don't come near!
Sorry.
Count us in!
Come here.
Come on.
Well, character.
Let me go. Let go.
I wasn't upset.
You said you were pretending.
You couldn't reveal yourself.
I got angry instead of you.
What? Well?
You are a wonderful actress.
Do you even know what this means?
Isn't it something good?
By the way, what is a fan club?
These are noble people
who wish someone happiness
and success from the bottom of my heart.
It's like a spiritual guide.
What about anti-fans?
Let me think.
Someone who is more interested in this person than a fan?
More influential mentor.
I don't deserve your feelings for me.
Give it up. If I'm deposed
I will sell kukpap.
Don't say that.
I won't let this happen.
I'm also your anti-fan.
Certainly. Calmed me down.
Now we go in different directions.
We have different goals.
Where is a good restaurant?
where do people line up?
“An” means convenient, “ti”...
fan?
I thought I had done well enough in my studies.
There is something to work on.
-Try it.
-God.
-Many.
-Buy it, madam.
-Try it.
-Buy it.
-What are you doing?
Delicious, I guess.
Scared me, what are you doing?
You'll go into a back alley in expensive clothes,
you will become a target.
-Which target?
-Who do we have here?
What have such rich people forgotten here?
This is what I was talking about.
Move away. I don't want to hurt you.
Do you like the girl?
In vain.
And don't even dream
that I'm here alone.
I've noticed this before.
You express yourself so awkwardly
like an educated robber.
-Be polite.
-Yeah.
Don't worry, I won't give you any offense.
I'm your anti-fan.
What did he say?
Scared.
Wherever I am
You should not walk in remote places.
Take care of them, Cheoljong.
And if something happens to him,
will history change?
Hey! I'm from the special forces!
Already lost?
Cheoljong.
Are you dead?
How can I get home?
Wow, why does a rich lady...
I thought she came back because she was worried about me.
And you just don’t know the way home.
What about those thugs?
They ran after the guy in more expensive clothes.
Don't worry, I won't give you any offense.
I'm your anti-fan.
What did he say?
Our time is not so peaceful
to turn your back.
I think you understand what you've gotten yourself into.
Come on. Just a poem.
From the Qing Empire?
It's beautiful if we sell it,
we can eat for five days.
Come on, take it off.
Don't turn your back.
I didn't kill him.
But I’ll definitely kill the next one who rushes.
Why is he on earth?
I just had too much to drink.
You are very lucky.
What about your clothes?
I can't go unnoticed
in expensive clothes.
What are you doing?
Need to buy something.
She left in a hurry and didn’t take the money.
-Great.
-You are robbing a robber.
Hey, no.
Show me. It's not fair to take everything for yourself.
Eat kukpapa.
Here you go.
- Let's go.
-What do you want to buy?
Continue.
He fought skillfully.
Judging by the way he guarded the room,
I think the item exists.
Will you be able to recognize him if you meet him again?
Certainly. Mister,
I need medicine.
I made it clear.
There is no cure if you fail.
How will you repay me?
Will you give your hand to be cut off?
I'll repay you.
I swear on my life.
Here! Guess what it is.
Moon vessel from the Goryeo Dynasty.
Seriously? It's such a value.
-What is the price?
-It's a fake copy.
Buy it if you plan to use it to protect yourself again.
Here's a crook.
Choose one.
I bet everything.
Wow, you can’t bet that much money.
This is a capitalist society
where money wins.
- I'll bet everything.
-Sorry.
-What are you doing?
-My lady.
Madam.
-Open it.
Such a fraudster must have
his gang is near the table.
I'm sure all the spectators are there for
to invite you into the game.
You were born a king.
And it still seems
you know the streets up and down.
And he denied it with all his might.
This is my weak point.
My family was destroyed under the pretext of treason.
Prince Ganghwado.
My family history is my weakness,
which destroys me.
Do you have nightmares about
How do you get scolded in court, or what?
A real nightmare is not what I dream.
A real nightmare...
Why did you stop mid-sentence?
I forgot what I was going to say.
Actually
I wanted to ask you a question.
Why didn't you tell anyone about that night?
-About what?
-That I tried to hurt you.
Oh, are you talking about this? I don't want to get into this mess.
I just want to slide past all the difficulties.
If only our country would become peaceful,
to be idle already.
Saving the country is not my thing at all.
There you go.
I would like to stand up and greet you.
Yes, I slept in the cold mountains,
my whole body hurts.
If I had stayed there one more night,
my lovely lips would go numb.
-Have you finished?
-What are you talking about?
Your whining.
And a little bragging.
I still have a lot of things
but I'll stop here -
It seems you have something important to do.
OK. What's there?
I heard you make the best masks.
Pick something there.
Wow, teethers...
I don't want a regular mask.
I'm thinking of selling to officials
unique masks.
Unique?
Lately you seem like mine
and at the same time no.
Pour water.
Yes!
-Royal cook.
-Yes?
The Dowager Queen wants a late snack.
But I'm not sure you can do it.
How are you...
I've been working in the royal kitchen for 30 years,
and 12 of them as a royal chef.
How can I be worse than the queen?
Sooner is better.
I trust you completely.
Crap. Again.
Again.
Faster.
This is all?
I milked all the cows in the barn.
There is not a drop of milk left.
Nonsense!
What?
You're an armless asshole.
Your Majesty.
I suddenly became so angry, everything infuriates me.
Not this confused body
nothing lying around like a dead man,
don't feel like me.
I don't even know, my name is Chan Soyeon
or Kim Bong Hwan.
Well, your memory has returned,
so you are confused.
Do you know what I hate most?
I'm getting used to this body.
That I feel comfortable in a skirt now.
You're probably on your period.
I'll get you some pads.
I have
menstruation?
Court Lady Jeon!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Why hasn't the queen returned to the palace yet?
I'll send another letter now.
We're not at war.
Send it as soon as it's light.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Is my brother's word no longer as powerful?
Old age is a vice.
How hungry I am.
Another.
There is no one.
Mr. Hon.
It's you. Come in.
Waiting for my return?
How did you know that I just returned?
Hey.
Wait a minute.
How did you get so wasted in 2 days?
Mr. Hon.
Have you lost all your money to the crooks?
Or have you lost your house documents?
I was 14 then, I was naive.
This problem is more serious.
Lost your documents for the site?
This already happened when I went...
Your family also suffered from misfortunes.
Family or love?
That's the question.
Poor guy.
You poor thing.
This is truly a serious problem.
Your Majesty. Dowager Queen
calls you quickly to the Dongmyeongjong hall.
Did you call me?
You don't believe that you're to blame
in the death of the late king, right?
So you do your best
to blame my family.
Your Majesty.
You can insult me any way you like.
but take care of our late king.
Again you are hiding behind my son.
Incredible, you have enough shamelessness
blame someone to hide guilt.
A person must know himself
not to commit
same errors twice.
Thank you for the lesson.
I'm so tired that I can't take off my socks.
I'll be happy to take them off for you.
Cart Day is coming soon.
At this time my patience will end.
I'm back.
Yes.
I heard that the Detective Department had a lot to do today.
They say you opposed the royal guards.
There were suspicions. I wanted to find
evidence before telling you.
There are suspicious people among the royal guards.
I think there are seven of them.
Did you know about them?
Do you think I didn't touch them because I didn't know about them?
If you are interested in them directly, how will they react?
They will dig a deeper hole and lie to the bottom.
They will become smarter and act secretly.
What can be seen is not a threat.
Make them believe that you don't see them.
And then you can kill them right away,
as soon as they become a problem.
I didn't think about it.
Do you think
the king is in this position simply because
that he has no abilities?
The reason is that I personally instilled fear in his mind.
It is easy to control those who are afraid.
If the one above is afraid of me,
my power exceeds his.
I will turn to you with questions concerning the king.
Go get some rest.
They won't be able to find you there.
I will definitely come back for you.
But until then, don't go out for anything.
What about my brothers? And you, mom?
I'm fine as long as you're alive.
You are my only son.
If you die
I can't live either.
Faster!
It seems so to me.
This is unrealistic.
We need to find the accounting book.
Am I wrong?
Impossible.
I'm innocent, Wonbeom!
I was falsely accused. Son, I can't rest.
Wonbom! Wonbom!
-It wasn't me.
-Wonbom.
-Only you survived.
-Unfair.
It's all a lie.
It's only in my head.
-No no.
-I curse you.
-No.
Kim Soyeon.
What? So similar.
Do you think you will become like the real Kim Soyeon?
They have something in common: no mothers.
This book was written by a scholar from Joseon.
Initial Instruction for Children
Kim Soyeon
Five types of relationships:
father - son, ruler - subject, husband - wife,
older brother, younger brother,
each other.
You study so hard that you wear out the book.
Why are you repeating it again?
Today is my mother's funeral.
This is her book.
So that's what you do when you miss your mom.
I cried
Until I found a way to see my mother.
Which?
If I die, I will see her.
Alive?
Did you come to die too?
What are you talking about?
I came here to die.
Do you want to live? Because you're afraid to die?
No.
Everyone dies except me. That's what's scary.
Then
let's die together.
Let's do this on the count of three.
Yes.
The sound is coming from here!
Brother?
Do you know how worried I was?
The whole family was looking for you.
Brother.
I'll come down to you.
Just lower the ladder.
Fine.
Sorry. But I still want to live.
You also want to live, right?
I'll come back.
If you want to live
if you want to live again, then give it back to me.
-Can you reach it?
-Yes.
Dad.
Please.
Mrs. Soyeon.
Dad, please. Daddy.
Daddy! Please!
Dad, daddy!
-Please.
-Lay the well.
Dad, no! No need, dad!
Dad! Don't do this!
No! Dad!
No need, dad! No need!
Please, dad! Don't do this!
Dad, no! Daddy!
Dad!
Both mom and this girl.
I still didn't believe their promises.
It will all end when I die.
It won't end until the well is filled with water.
Never.
Save me!
Save, save me!
Save! Please!
Sorry! Please save me!
It's my fault.
He will die because of me.
Because I revealed the secret.
I told the maid about him.
Did you hear what the adults said?
His family are traitors.
But he didn't do anything.
Brother, you're a good person, aren't you?
Please, brother.
Come here quickly.
My brother is truly a good person.
Save. Save me.
Please. Save.
We need to hurry.
You really are back.
As promised.
I want to live.
So are you.
Kim Soyeon
People are afraid of the dark
so they turn on the light.
Secret
But the brighter the light,
the blacker the shadow.
Hwajin.
What happened?
That's right, I almost touched him.
It was dangerous.
You could come whenever you wanted.
But you can't act as you want.
I'm sure it's fake.
You say someone faked their identity?
I will defeat one enemy with the help of another.
This is how I will become indispensable:
Korean food and Korean self-care.
Fear and anxiety take away your sanity.
You really are my anti-fan.
I was worried about a lot of things, but I found a way out.